Guide to the William S. Vickrey Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Manuscripts
  - Subseries III.8: Transportation
    - Schedules for Buenos Aires Suburban Service, notes (Box 29, Folder 499)
      [Includes actual proposed schedule. ]
    - Seats for All on the Subway, paper (Box 29, Folder 500)
    - Sketch of Proposal for a Study of Street Use Pricing, outline, 5 Nov. 1970 (Box 29, Folder 501)
    - Social Costs of Transportation: Their Meaning and Use in the Allocation of Resources, paper, 22 Jan. 1980 (Box 29, Folder 502)
    - Some Suggestions for Open Platform Fare Collection, paper, March 1962 (Box 29, Folder 503)
      [Discusses suburban service. ]
    - Some Suggestions for Suburban Fare Collection, essay, March 1962 (Box 29, Folder 504)
    - Some Suggestions for the Pricing of the Caracas Metro, fragment, Jan. 1982 (Box 29, Folder 505)
    - Specifications and Procedures for the Construction of a Consolidated Quick-Reference Airlines Timetable, paper, ca. 1968 (Box 29, Folder 506)
      [Includes algorithm for itineraries, notes, and examples.]
    - Statement to Joint Committee on Washington Metropolitan Problems, paper, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 507)
      [An abridged version of the testimony was prepared for publication. Contains original proposal for finely adjusted congestion pricing with automatic vehicle identified (AVI) units and roadside scanning points.]
    - Statement to New York State Assembly Standing Committee on Transportation, transcript, 3 Oct. 1979 (Box 30, Folder 508)
      [Disputes the disposition of the "Energy Conservation Bond Issue".]
    - Subway Automation, paper (Box 30, Folder 509)
    - A Suggested Fare Structure and Fare Collection Program, paper, 26 July 1962 (Box 30, Folder 510)
    - Suggestions for New Subway Maps, fragment, Feb. 1978 (Box 30, Folder 511)
    - Tarifacion del Uso de Las Calles, Tema No. 8, lecture notes, 12 July 1976, (langcode="spa">Spanish) (Box 30, Folder 512)
    - La Tarification des Transports Urbains: Principes Économiques, Possibilitiés Techniques, Astreintes Politiques, fragment, 5 Nov. 1973, (langcode="spa">Spanish) (Box 30, Folder 513)
    - Testimony before a New York Committee, transcript, ca. 1992 (Box 30, Folder 514)
    - Testimony before the Federal Highway Administration in the Matter of Bayonne Bridge, George Washington Bridge, Goethals Bridge and Outerbridge Crossing Tolls, Docket No. 76-9, transcript (Box 30, Folder 515)
      [Submitted on behalf of The Environmental Defense Fund.]
    - Testimony on behalf of the Environmental Defense Fund concerning PATH fares, transcript (Box 30, Folder 516)
    - Traffic Measures to Reduce Air Pollution, paper, Feb. 1987 (Box 30, Folder 517)
    - Transfers, notes (Box 30, Folder 518)
    - Transit Automation (Tehran), notes (Box 30, Folder 519)
    - Transit Fare Action Program, essay, 28 March 1973 (Box 30, Folder 520)
    - Two Means of Alleviating Rush-Hour Crowding: A Discussion, paper, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 521)
      [Published in Transportation and Engineering Journal, May 1975, 395-9. Suggests that the skip-stop operation plus trains 30 percent longer than standard platforms could increase seating capacity by 70 percent, superior to the suggestion of Charles Libove, Ibid. Nov. 1973 for double-stopping of double-length trains, or eliminating seats altogether.]
    - Types of Congestion Pricing Models, paper, Nov. 1994 (Box 30, Folder 522)
      [Summary review and classification including discussion of turbulence, triggernecks, traffic lights, stochasticity, and bathtub models.]
    - The Use of Tolls in Controlling Urban Traffic Congestion, paper, Nov. 1972 (Box 30, Folder 523)
      [For Unorthodox Approaches to Urban Transportation: The Emerging Challenge to Conventional Planning, Bureau of Business and Economic Research, Georgia State University, Atlanta, 16-17 Nov. 1972, pp. 22-37.]
  - Subseries III.9: Urban Economics
    Papers, reviews, models, and notes proposing resolutions to urban issues. Includes descriptions of the efficient city, urban development, taxation, land valuation, transportation, and strategies for making New York City work. Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - The Allocation to Land to Transportation, paper, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 524)
      [Includes Appendix A. One Dimensional Model of Area Optimization.]
    - The City as a Firm, paper, 1964 & 1977 (Box 30, Folder 525)
      [Published in The Economics of Public Services. Proceedings of a Conference Held by the International Economics Association at Turin. Edited by Martin S. Feldstein and Robert F. Inman. London: MacMillian, New York: Wiley, 1977. The original locus of the thesis that in a world of perfect competition among cities, urban land rents in each city will be just sufficient to finance the subsidies required to permit marginal cost pricing of the goods and services produced under conditions of increasing returns to scale, the availability of which is responsible for the agglomeration of the city. See also The Efficient City, Box 30, Folder 528.]
    - Comments regarding "Goals for NYC", second draft (Box 30, Folder 526)
    - Defining Land Value for Tax Purposes, paper, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 527)
      [Published in The Assessment of Land Value. A Symposium sponsored by the Committee on Taxation, Resources and Economic Development. Edited by Daniel M. Holland. Madison, London: University of Wisconsin Press, 1970. Discusses practical and conceptual problems in assessing land values, the notion of a standard condition, problems of parcels in substantially substandard condition, and the effects of assembly or subdivision, internalization of externalities in large holdings.]
    - The Efficient City, paper (Box 30, Folder 528)
      [Establishes the relationship between land rents and transport costs. See also The City as a Firm, Box 30, Folder 525.]
    - Externalities in Urban Development, paper, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 529)
      [Published in Proceedings of the American Real Estate and Urban Economics Association. 1969. An initial foreshadowing of the thesis relating urban land rents to subsidies needed for marginal cost pricing and the problems with decentralization of efficient allocation.]
    - Financing City Government..., fragment (Box 31, Folder 530)
    - Henry George, Economies of Scale and Land Taxation, paper, 9 Jan. 1992 (Box 31, Folder 531)
      [For COPE Meeting, 9 Jan. 1992.]
    - The Impact on Land Values of Taxing Buildings, paper, Sept. 1969 (Box 31, Folder 532)
      [Published in Proceedings of the 62nd National Tax Conference, Boston, Sept. 29-Oct. 3, 1969. Columbus, Ohio: National Tax Association. Contains a concentric model in which taxing buildings lowers land values at the centre and increases them in the periphery. See also Notes on the Land Tax, Box 31, Folder 538.]
    - Land Values and Economics of Scale in the Urban Environment, paper (Box 31, Folder 533)
    - Making New York City Function, paper, 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 534)
    - Making New York City Work, paper, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 535)
      [Published in Challenges of the Changing Economy of New York City, 1992. New York: Baruch College, New York City Council on Economic Education, 1992. Discusses market-clearing parking charges, time-of-day bridge and tunnel tolls, congestion charges, replacement of business and improvement taxes by land taxes, bringing utility rates and transit fares closer to marginal social cost, improving transit service, and shifting from incarceration to strict parole conditions, strictly enforced by electronic devices and low cash loads. Also includes bathtub model.]
    - Notes for the panel on New York City in Crisis--Causes Encampment for Citizenship, notes, 16 Sept. 1976 (Box 31, Folder 536)
    - Notes on "Road Pricing Techniques" by Kiran Bhatt, review, Feb. 1974 (Box 31, Folder 537)
    - Notes on the Land Tax, notes (Box 31, Folder 538)
      [See also The Impact on Land Values of Taxing Buildings, Box 31, Folder 532.]
    - Notes re Unsuspected Perversities in the Theory of Location by Richard G. Lipsey and Curtis Eaton, book review, Sept. 1972 (Box 31, Folder 539)
    - Optimum Cities as Efficient Competitive Firms, paper, Oct. 1973 (Box 31, Folder 540)
      [For conference on Econometrics and Mathematical Economics, Georgetown University. Discusses GHV theorem and decentralization.]
    - Propositions Relating to Site Value Taxation, paper, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 541)
      [For TRED, 29-30 Sept. and Levy Institute, 2-4 Nov.]
    - La Renta de Terrenos Urbanos Como Fuente de Subvenciones de Servicios de Naturaleza Local, Tema No. 14, lecture notes, 20 July 1976, (langcode="spa">Spanish) (Box 31, Folder 542)
    - Site Value Taxes and Public Services, notes, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 543)
      [Notes for a talk at St. John's University, 17 Oct. 1991. Argues that in an imperfect world, a city which priced public services at marginal cost would reap the gains.]
    - Subroutine for Computing the Area of a Polygon containing all points that are closer to a given point then to any of N other points in a plane, notes (Box 31, Folder 544)
    - Transition Effects of Shifting to a Land Tax, notes, June 1970 (Box 31, Folder 545)
    - Urban Issues: Some Novel Solutions, notes, 10 Nov. 1981 (Box 31, Folder 546)
      [Notes for talk at Scarsdale Adult School, 10 Nov. 1991]
    - Urban Model, notes (Box 31, Folder 547)
    - Urban Street Model, notes (Box 31, Folder 548)
    - The Use of Land for Transportation, paper, Feb. 1964 (Box 31, Folder 549)
      [Previously announced title "The Social Opportunity Cost of Land". Paper prepared for the Second Conference on Urban Public Expenditure at New York University, sponsored by the Committee on Urban Economics of Resources for the Future, Inc., 21-22 Feb. 1964. Discusses in freight transport and raises issues of unpriced congestion.]
    - User Charges as Alternatives to Building Taxes, paper, March 1971 (Box 31, Folder 550)
      [Discusses education, police, pollution, urban transport (trucks), and utilities. See also General and Specific Financing of Urban Services, Box 46, Folder 760.]
  - Subseries III.10: Miscellaneous
    Papers, notes, reviews, essays, statements, lists, teaching materials, and fragments about assorted subjects of interest to Vickrey. Contains discussions of theory, insurance, public services, foreign economic systems, conflict resolution, computer applications, methods of economic measurement, higher education, politics, sociology, and minor diversions. Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Algebra, notes (Box 32, Folder 551)
    - Bons Mots, notes (Box 32, Folder 552)
    - Cargas Que Varien Segun el Ingreso del Pagante, Tema No. 12, lecture notes, 1976, (langcode="spa">Spanish) (Box 32, Folder 553)
    - Causality, Control, and Observation, paper (Box 32, Folder 554)
      [Includes comments on paper by H. Wold.]
    - Classifications and Codes, list, 1956 & 1962 (Box 32, Folder 555)
    - Comments on "Investment, Dividend, and External Finance Behavior of Firms" by Phoebus J. Dhrymes and Mordecai Kurz, and on "Business Fixed Investment: A Marriage of Fact and Fancy" by W. H. Locke Anderson, review (Box 32, Folder 556)
      [Discusses produced durables.]
    - Curiosa, notes (Box 32, Folder 557)
    - Definition and Measurement of Risk, fragment (Box 32, Folder 558)
    - The Definition and Measurement of Risk: Individual, Social and Market Risk, paper, 19 Oct. 1967 (Box 32, Folder 559)
      [For Institute for Quantitative Research in Finance, Montreal, 19 Oct. 1967]
    - Democracy Beyond Majority Rule, paper, 9 Feb. 1995 (Box 32, Folder 560)
    - Economic Solutions and Political Hurdles (An Economist's Utopia), paper, [1992] (Box 32, Folder 561)
      [Presented as The Frank Tannenbaum Lecture to the 48th Annual Meeting of the University Seminars at Columbia University, 22 April 1992. Brief statement with equations on cumulative averaging and background to innovative failures.]
    - An Economist's View of Human Rights, notes, 9 March 1978 (Box 32, Folder 562)
      [Notes for talk to General Education Seminar. Provides insight into Vickrey's moral views.]
    - Eye Twisters, sketches (Box 32, Folder 563)
    - Factors Underlying Soviet and Western Growth and their Implications, notes (Box 32, Folder 564)
      [Notes related to Russia and peace.]
    - Figgerin, notes (Box 32, Folder 565)
    - File Classifications, notes (Box 32, Folder 566)
    - Financianento de la Ensenanza Superior, Tema No. 13, lecture notes, 19 July 1976, (langcode="spa">Spanish) (Box 32, Folder 567)
      [Discusses financing higher education.]
    - The Generalized Queen's Problem, notes (Box 32, Folder 568)
    - Increased Minimum Wage Could Increase Employment, letter to the editor, 6 April 1996 (Box 32, Folder 569)
    - Issues in Student Loan Programs, paper, Dec. 1966 (Box 32, Folder 570)
    - Letter to Editorial Board of MEASURE, letter, 28 Dec. 1976 (Box 32, Folder 571)
      [Argues against tenure.]
    - Lumber Model, notes (Box 32, Folder 572)
    - Matrix Algebra sans Determinants, notes (Box 32, Folder 573)
      [Illustrates Vickrey's mathematical creativity.]
    - Medical Insurance and Employment Burdens, essay, 22 May 1994 (Box 32, Folder 574)
      [Argues against using a payroll tax to finance medical insurance and makes the point that making medical insurance part of payroll tax is distortionary.]
    - MLS, fragment (Box 32, Folder 575)
    - My Innovative Failures in Economics, address, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 576)
      [Presidential Address to the Atlantic Economic Association, Plymouth, Mass., 16 Oct. 1992. Published in Atlantic Economic Journal, March 1993, 1-9. Discusses tax reform, marginal cost pricing, and full employment. See also How Successful as Innovators Have Economists Been?, Box 14, Folder 223.]
    - A Note on "Qualifying Requirements" in Unemployment Insurance, essay, 8 Sept. 1967 (Box 32, Folder 577)
      [Discusses adverse selection and argues against stiffening requirements.]
    - Notes and Comments on the February 20, 1967 draft of the memorandum on An Educational Opportunity Bank from the panel on Educational Research and Development, review, ca. 1967 (Box 33, Folder 578)
    - Notes on "Impact of Competition..." by Chapman, review (Box 33, Folder 579)
    - Notes on "Issue-Elasticity in Political Systems" by Strickland and Johnston, review (Box 33, Folder 580)
    - Notes on "On Search and Equilibrium Price Distributions" by J. E. Stiglitz, review, 19 Aug. 1980 (Box 33, Folder 581)
    - Notes on Operations, notes (Box 33, Folder 582)
      [Apparently algorithms developed for numerical illustrations.]
    - Notes on "Putting Americans Back to Work" by Maco Stewart, review, 17 March 1993 (Box 33, Folder 583)
    - Notes on "Rehabilitating Cardinal Utility" by R. Cooter, review (Box 33, Folder 584)
    - Notes on the Financing of Health Services, notes, 16 Sept. 1993 (Box 33, Folder 585)
      [Discusses typology of pure forms.]
    - Notes on "Welfare Foundations of Congestion Economics" by McGillivray, review (Box 33, Folder 586)
    - Outline of Topics for MIT Urban Seminar, notes, Aug. 1977 (Box 33, Folder 587)
    - The Pareto Optimality of Competitive Equilibrium, paper (Box 33, Folder 588)
    - Pastimes, notes, ca. 1969 (Box 33, Folder 589)
    - Personal Notes and References, notes (Box 33, Folder 590)
      [Mainly names and telephone numbers.]
    - A Proposal for Financing Higher Education, paper, 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 591)
    - Puzzles, notes, 1949-1966 (Box 33, Folder 592)
    - Report on Mission to Zambia, paper, June 1975 (Box 33, Folder 593)
      [For United Nations. Contains practical recommendations for applying cumulative averaging, marginal cost pricing, etc.]
    - Returns and Homogeneity: A Clarification, paper (Box 33, Folder 594)
    - Review of India's Green Revolution: Economic Gains and Political Costs by Francine R. Frankel, book review, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 595)
    - The Sociology of Concentration Camps, report, Sept. 1950 (Box 33, Folder 596)
      [Preliminary report on a research project under the auspices of The Columbia Social Science Research Council and presented at the Conference on World War II in the West, Amsterdam, 4-9 Sept. 1950.]
    - Some Additional Thoughts after perusing Cartter's "Some Financial Implications...", essay (Box 33, Folder 597)
    - Some Notes on Computer Repertoires, with Special Reference to UNIVAC II and 1105, paper, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 598)
    - Some Notes on Current Economic Condition, notes, June 1980 (Box 33, Folder 599)
      [Argues that unemployment is worse than inflation.]
    - Some Notes on the Theory and Practice of Sorting on Digital Computers, paper, 1 Nov. 1959 (Box 33, Folder 600)
    - Sorting in the Light of Information Theory: Some New Techniques, paper, July 1965 (Box 34, Folder 601)
      [Related to the problem of processing data for congestion pricing.]
    - Sorting on Digital Computers--Some Notes Based on Information Theory, notes, April 1964 (Box 34, Folder 602)
    - Sources of Turbulence in Conflict Situations, notes, 26 Oct. 1976 (Box 34, Folder 603)
      [Notes for the University Seminar on Peace, 26 Oct. 1976]
    - Statement at Hearings on Price Statistics of the Federal Government Joint Economic Committee, Subcommittee on Economic Statistics, statement, 5 May 1961 (Box 34, Folder 604)
      [Disagrees with Stigler Committee on treatment of insurance.]
    - Statement before the Water Resources Subcommittee of the U.S. Senate Committee on Public Works, statement, 1 April 1977 (Box 34, Folder 605)
      [Concerns user charges on Island Waterways. Includes statement of why Vickrey considers efficiency to be of paramount importance.]
    - Temas a Elaborarse por el Dr. Vickrey, Caracas, outline, ca. 1976, (langcode="spa">Spanish) (Box 34, Folder 606)
    - Teoria del Progression, Tema No. 17, lecture notes, 22 July 1976, (langcode="spa">Spanish) (Box 34, Folder 607)
    - Testimony on Cable before the NYC Board of Estimates, speech, 21 June 1983 (Box 34, Folder 608)
      [Argues for better regulation in New York City.]
    - Theoretical Economics, bibliography, ca. 1964 (Box 34, Folder 609)
    - Theoretical Economics, illustrations, ca. 1964 (Box 34, Folder 610)
    - Theoretical Economics, outline, ca. 1964 (Box 34, Folder 611)
    - Theory and Welfare Notes, notes (Box 34, Folder 612)
    - Theory Teaching Program, notes, 1946 & 1953 (Box 34, Folder 613)
    - Tic Tac Toe, notes (Box 34, Folder 614)
      [Attempts to algorithmize.]
    - The University Economist and the Labor Movement, paper (Box 34, Folder 615)
    - Venezuela Course, notes, 1976, (langcode="spa">Spanish) (Box 34, Folder 616)
      [Mainly rough drafts of lecture notes and exams.]
    - Miscellaneous Fragments, fragments (Box 34, Folder 617)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, notes (Box 34, Folder 618)
      [Notes on half a dozen different problems.]
- Series IV: Columbia University
  Correspondence with administrators, fellow professors, students, visitors, librarians, and others involved in university activities. Also includes exams, papers, course syllabi, reading lists, seminar presentations, and other teaching materials used by Vickrey during his career. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Ad Hoc Committees, 1960-1970 (Box 35, Folder 619)
  - Appointments, 1948-1975 (Box 35, Folder 620)
  - Barger, Harold, 1961-1963 (Box 35, Folder 621)
  - Bookstore, 1948-1979 (Box 35, Folder 622)
  - Cobun, Nancy, 1955-1956 (Box 35, Folder 623)
  - Conferences on the Humanities and Public Policy Issues, 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 624)
  - Correspondence, 1947-1969 (Box 35, Folder 625)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1992, undated (Box 35, Folder 626)
  - Course Evaluations (Box 35, Folder 627)
  - Dissertations, 1947-1987 (Box 35, Folder 628)
  - Economic Analysis Course, 1954-1965, undated (Box 35, Folder 629)
  - Economics 101 Course, 1954-1959, undated (Box 35, Folder 630)
  - Economics 103 Course, 1953, undated (Box 35, Folder 631)
  - Economics 105 Course (Box 35, Folder 632)
  - Economics 1103 Course, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 633)
  - Economics 2080 Course, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 634)
  - Graduate School of Business, 1948-1993 (Box 35, Folder 635)
  - Grant Squires Prize, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 636)
  - Leaves of Absence, 1949-1978 (Box 36, Folder 637)
  - Libraries, 1949-1971 (Box 36, Folder 638)
  - Meetings and Visitors, 1960-1992 (Box 36, Folder 639)
  - Microeconomics Course, 1969-1979, undated (Box 36, Folder 640)
  - Office of the Registrar, 1947-1984 (Box 36, Folder 641)
  - Padawar-Singer, Alice M. 1973 (Box 36, Folder 642)
  - Parking, 1968-1982 (Box 36, Folder 643)
  - Peace Seminars, 1956-1977 (Box 36, Folder 644)
  - PhD in Religion, 1953-1961 (Box 36, Folder 645)
  - Proposal for Research Program on Railroad Transportation, 7 Jan. 1965 (Box 36, Folder 646)
  - Public Finance Course: Exams, 1974-1984 (Box 36, Folder 647)
  - Public Finance Course: Notes, 1975-1979, undated (Box 36, Folder 648)
  - Public Finance Course: Reading Lists, 1971-1981 (Box 36, Folder 649)
  - Public Finance Course: Syllabi, 1970-1980 (Box 36, Folder 650)
  - Reading Lists, 1965, undated (Box 36, Folder 651)
  - References, 1947-1986 (Box 37, Folder 652)
  - Sabbatical, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 653)
  - Salary and Benefits, 1947-1977 (Box 37, Folder 654)
  - Sea Grant, 1968-1971 (Box 37, Folder 655)
  - Students, 1947-1981 (Box 37, Folder 656)
  - Theory and Welfare Seminar, 7 June 1960 (Box 37, Folder 657)
  - University Seminars, 1953-1960 (Box 37, Folder 658)
  - University Seminars, 1961-1964 (Box 37, Folder 659)
  - University Seminars, 1965-1995 (Box 37, Folder 660)
  - Urban Economics Course: Exams, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 661)
  - Urban Economics Course: Reading Lists, 1970-1975, undated (Box 37, Folder 662)
  - Urban Land Use and Transportation Course: Exams, 1970-1981 (Box 38, Folder 663)
  - Urban Land Use and Transportation Course: Notes (Box 38, Folder 664)
  - Urban Land Use and Transportation Course: Reading Lists, 1971-1983, undated (Box 38, Folder 665)
  - Urban Land Use and Transportation Course: Syllabi, 1969-1983 (Box 38, Folder 666)
  - Welfare Economics and Utility Regulation Course: Exams (Box 38, Folder 667)
  - Welfare Economics and Utility Regulation Course: Notes (Box 38, Folder 668)
  - Welfare Economics and Utility Regulation Course: Reading Lists, 1972-1984 (Box 38, Folder 669)
  - Welfare Economics and Utility Regulation Course: Syllabi, 1972-1985 (Box 38, Folder 670)
  - Welfare Economics Course, 1965-1982 (Box 38, Folder 671)
  - Welfare Economics of Price Structures Course: Exams, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 672)
  - Welfare Economics of Price Structures Course: Notes, 1954, undated (Box 38, Folder 673)
  - Welfare Economics of Price Structures Course: Reading Lists, 1954-1961 (Box 38, Folder 674)
  - Welfare Economics of Price Structures Course: Syllabi, 1954-1961 (Box 38, Folder 675)
- Series V: Conference Materials
  Programs, schedules, correspondence, publicity, discussion transcripts, and related materials about the participants, travel arrangements, topics to be debated, chairmanship duties, and comments on proposed presentations. Includes correspondence and other papers about the American Economic Association (AEA) 1991 Annual Meeting organized by Vickrey. The meeting files detail the proposed sessions, papers submitted for presentation, organization of joint programs, and further planning information. Arranged alphabetically by conference title.
  - American Economic Association (AEA) 1961 Annual Meeting, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 676)
  - American Economic Association (AEA) 1991 Annual Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 677)
  - American Economic Association (AEA) 1991 Annual Meeting: Acceptance Letters, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 678)